export interface Question {
    question: string;
    answers: string[];
    correctAnswerIndex: number;
}

export const questions: Question[] = [
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Rectify"',
        answers: ['To build', 'Correct', 'Destroy', 'To command'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Parasite"',
        answers: ['A loss of motion', 'Exterminator', 'Disease', 'One that clings'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Placate"',
        answers: ['To make sure', 'To annoy', 'To pacify', 'To flatten out'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Paramount"',
        answers: ['Very important', 'Wide and extensive', 'Above others in rank of authority', 'Famous'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Forestall"',
        answers: ['Avoid', 'Frighten', 'Prevent', 'Disappoint'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Acumen"',
        answers: ['Abundance', 'Bitterness', 'Deficit', 'Quickness of insight'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Nascent"',
        answers: ['Initial', 'Unpleasant', 'Latest', 'Crude'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Interim"',
        answers: ['Temporary', 'Internal', 'Timely', 'Interval'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Perspicacious"',
        answers: ['Bad', 'Clear', 'Hazy', 'Shrewd'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Incensed"',
        answers: ['Affected', 'Incited', 'Encouraged', 'Inspired'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Mitigate"',
        answers: ['Send on a mission', 'Pardon', 'Soften', 'To heal'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Diatribe"',
        answers: ['Address', 'Attack', 'Discharge', 'Objection'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Sensuous"',
        answers: ['Aesthetic', 'Abundant', 'Delicious', 'Imposing'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Denounce"',
        answers: ['Condemn', 'Maintain', 'Sustain', 'Support'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Enigmatic"',
        answers: ['Illusive', 'Complicated', 'Puzzling', 'Pithy'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Prohibitive"',
        answers: ['Swanky', 'Unaffordable', 'Fancy', 'Closed'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Chivalrous"',
        answers: ['Improverished', 'Impetuous', 'Gallant', 'Brave'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Venerate"',
        answers: ['Accuse', 'Abuse', 'Respect', 'Defame'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Fulsome"',
        answers: ['Excessive', 'Liberal', 'Generous', 'Smooth'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Choose a synonym of "Reward"',
        answers: ['Forfeiture', 'Demotion', 'Penalty', 'Retribution'],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3
    },
];
